Morning.
Helicopter company. Cool.
I see no yellow tape, no solemn cops.
Why are we here, Lisbon?
I don't know, Jane.
All I know is the director
called me at 4:30 a.m.
and asked me to handle this personally,
whatever this is.
And you just do
whatever the director says
- no questions asked?
- Uh, he's the director.
Okay, well, call me
when you figure it out.
Hey. Wait. No, he asked
for you specifically, too.
I take this nap for freedom, Lisbon
for every little guy who has a dream.
Nap later.
Now we fight crime.
- No. I'm napping now.
- Agent Lisbon.
- Mr. Jane.
- Hi.
Garth Drucker, Head of Security
for Mr. Bajoran.
Guess I nap for freedom
a little later.
Our C.E.O. Yuri Bajoran received
a call just after midnight.
It was a computerized voice telling him
to put his affairs in order
and that he'd be killed
in the next 24 hours.
Hang on. Wait.
A death threat?
Usually we only get the case
once there's actually
been, uh, a death
so your boss, Mr. Bajoran, has
obviously pulled some strings
to get us here.
No. No. Mr. Bajoran didn't want
the police. He was adamant.
Well, someone asked for Agent Lisbon
and me specifically
and that someone
must be very powerful
probably very rich, someone like, uh...
Walter Mashburn?
Thank heavens you're here,
Patrick and Agent...
- Lisbon.
- Lisbon. Right.
Good to see you.
- Did you bring us here?
- I did.
Poor Yuri's in danger.
Now I'm acquiring
his company today
and I can't have him expire
before he signs the contract.
You know them?
Oh, just a little misunderstanding
last year.
For a brief moment, uh
Walter was a murder suspect
in one of our cases.
Didn't do it.
Mr. Mashburn,
we're sworn officers of the law.
We're not your own personal
private investigators.
Well, when I heard Yuri
was in trouble
naturally I wanted the best
in law enforcement.
I take the threat against him
very seriously.
Right, Yuri?
Let's sign the contract, Walter.
I wanna start spending
my new fortune.
Yuri Bajoran.
Don't make yourself comfortable.
You won't be here long.
I'm Agent Lisbon, Mr. Bajoran.
We're here about the threat.
Forget the threat. It's a prank,
a scam. I'm a wealthy man.
- I get threats. End of story.
- No. He's worried.
It's fascinating how
this man can read people.
Like magic, really.
Wish I had the skill.
I doubt the insights
of a state employee
are all that remarkable.
Let's go, Walter.
Uh, you're former military
uh, ex-Special Forces
from some Baltic nation
possibly, uh, former K.G.B.
but in short, you're just
a thug in a rug.
- I apologize, sir. He doesn't...
- And despite your impatience
the last thing you feel like doing
is this deal, because, uh
you don't like Walter
and Walter doesn't like you.
Is he great or what?
You've wasted enough of my time.
Sign the contract now, Walter.
Drucker, with me.
Don't be such a baby, Yuri.
I'm sorry.
Ah. Looks like I might get that nap sooner
rather than later.
Shall we?
Let's do the damn deal, Walter.
Teresa, hey.
While you're here maybe you and I
could get together sometime soon...
Lisbon?
Help! Help!
Check on that right now!
Oh, stop it. You're fine.
- He's fine, right?
- He will be.
And that guy's got a pretty
bad laceration, but he'll live.
I'll live, Teresa. Did you hear that?
I'm alive. It's fantastic.
Yes, it is. Enjoy the adrenaline
while it lasts.
Hey, boss. So I spoke
to the arson unit commander.
He said it was a massive
subsonic explosive device
probably C-4 or Semtex.
A giant bomb, Rigsby. Just...
just say it's a giant bomb.
Yeah, or a giant bomb.
The blast seat was
under the conference table
made a crater
the size of a minivan.
- If I hadn't left when I did, then...
- Yeah, you'd be vaporized, too.
Flirting with Lisbon...
that's what saved him.
- He wasn't flirting with me.
- I wasn't flirting.
Any indication
of terrorist involvement?
Uh, no. It was a very specific,
targeted detonation.
- To kill Yuri.
- Yeah, and they succeeded.
Forensics found
enough remains...barely...
to identify Bajoran
and his Head of Security.
Drucker. Poor guy.
I told Yuri we should move
the meeting to my office
but he flat-out refused.
Stubborn old bull.
Someone threatens Yuri
wanting to frighten him
before killing him.
Who hated him that much?
Oh! Oh! I know that one.
Huh?
If I killed him, Teresa,
why would I call in the CBI?
You like games, thrills,
Mr. Mashburn.
Walter, please.
Mr. Mashburn was my mother.
I almost died myself.
Yeah, but you escaped
at the very last moment.
That was lucky.
True.
I guess I do look suspicious.
Sit down.
Don't take this personally.
I have to ask these questions.
Do you have the knowledge
and the resources to build a bomb?
Yes. But you know that already,
don't you?
My first company, Mashburn Avionics
made high-tech weaponry.
But I started out with cherry bombs
in the toilets at reform school.
You went to reform school?
My teachers thought
I was incorrigible.
But you know that, too.
Have you ever visited
Bajoran's Helicopter Plant
or solicited anybody
to go there?
You mean, to plant a bomb?
No, ma'am. Never have.
The threat to Yuri Bajoran was made
from a disposable phone
that was purchased
at a drugstore in Marin County.
Where I have a place...
Along with 250,000 other people.
Look, Teresa,
I didn't need to kill Yuri.
I'd already done worse.
I destroyed him.
- By taking over his company?
- His flagship.
Yuri and I had been
at each other for years
and I had finally won.
Don't you see?
I'd forced him
to sell me his baby.
Although he died before
he signed the contract.
I know. The bastard.
It's like he reached out from the grave
to deny me one last time.
But bottom line... I beat him
and I wanted him waking up for the next
30 years thinking about that.
You hated him so much
you wanted him alive?
Exactly.
Yuri Bajoran was a bad man, Teresa.
So who wanted him dead?
Who didn't? Aside from me.
His widow?
Marie? No. Fair point.
She seemed to love him
for some reason.
You know her?
I was engaged to her, actually,
years back.
She married Yuri instead.
Great lady.
Despite that tragic lapse
in judgment, a great lady.
How was the marriage?
Oh, you'd have to ask her.
So, Teresa, I'm tired of doing
this whole suspect thing again.
Not fun at all.
How about I play Detective this time
give you and Patrick a hand?
- Not a chance.
- Oh, never say "never."
Never, Walter. Never ever.
That's a maybe.
So you were engaged to Walter Mashburn
before you married Yuri?
That was years ago.
Why would you ask that?
Oh, nosy.
Did you dump him
or did he dump you? And why?
It's none of your business.
I fell in love with Yuri
is all I'll say.
I know what people said about him
but they were wrong.
He was a wonderful, loving person.
Interesting woman.
Didn't kill Yuri.
Um, I'm sorry.
Where's the bathroom?
- This way.
- Thank you.
Sorry for your loss.
- Who is that man?
- It's a long story.
Now, Mrs. Bajoran, who would
want your husband dead?
Yuri was a powerful man.
Powerful men have enemies.
This takeover by Mashburn...
is it true your husband
didn't want to sell?
Walter tricked him.
It wasn't right.
Tricked him how?
He approached someone
Yuri thought was a friend
and got him to secretly
buy up enough shares
so that Walter could force
the takeover.
- Name?
- Markham Shankar
software mogul.
Turns out he'd secretly
hated Yuri for years
some ridiculous business dispute
he wouldn't forgive.
Ma'am, you have a lovely home.
It's very, uh, cozy.
Thanks for having us.
Cho, we should... go.
Thank you.
Been a pleasure.
According to the Marin D.A.'s Office
Markham Shankar had good reason
to hate Bajoran.
Six years ago, he claimed Bajoran
cheated him out of a couple million bucks
he even tried to get the D.A.'s office
to file fraud charges.
Did you talk to him yet?
I can't even find him. No one's
photographed Shankar since 2002.
The guy's a recluse.
His office won't even admit
he's in the country.
Keep looking into it.
- And you...
- Hello, Lisbon.
What a great day
to not be blown up.
- Give it up now.
- Give what up?
What you took
from Bajoran's house.
The toupee, Jane.
The housekeeper called.
That's just gross.
Why would you take it?
- Evidence.
- Of what?
Bad taste.
Let me explain something.
You do not mess
with super-rich people.
They're like kids
with machine guns.
- Super-rich people, like Mashburn?
- What about Mashburn?
Oh, my God. You're just
so obsessed with Mashburn.
- You're the one who brought him up.
- What is it with you and him?
Got something. Whenever Shankar
is in San Francisco
he likes to stay
at Chaparral Glen.
- What's that?
- Country Club.
The most exclusive in California.
It's 100 grand to join.
They've got a 2,300-acre campus
in the woods.
Shankar likes "glamping."
You know, glamorous camping?
- You made that up.
- Did not.
Glamping... I like it.
Lisbon, shall we go and talk
to some more super-rich people?
Do something with that.
I'm sorry, Agent, but I can't tell you
if Mr. Shankar is here
and unless you have a search warrant
I can't allow you on the grounds.
Our members are quite concerned
about privacy.
I'm concerned about
a double homicide, sir.
- Hey, Walter.
- Hey, Patrick. Teresa.
Walter's a member here.
I thought we might need his help.
Mr. Trevayne
my friends Patrick and Teresa
will be joining us here today.
Sir, that won't be necessary.
We have your card on file.
What's the limit on that thing?
I don't know if there is one.
- Go find old Shankar, then?
- Let's.
Never say "never."
You know, Shankar's campsite
is right up on that ridge over there.
You can see the whole valley
from there.
This campsite... you want it.
You wish you owned it.
- I do. How'd you know?
- Pupil dilation.
- Pupil dilation?
- Yes.
When someone sees something they want
their pupils dilate.
Pupil dilation.
- Fantastic.
- Yes, it is.
Thank you.
Tell us about Markham Shankar.
Is he still mad at Yuri
about the fraud?
Oh, you bet.
Angry guy... Markham.
When I offered him the right incentive
he was very happy to betray Yuri.
What incentive can you offer a rich man
that he can't buy for himself?
A propeller from a
Beech Bonanza airplane.
Come again?
It was the only remaining piece
of the plane Buddy Holly died in.
Markham's obsessed
with celebrity deaths
has a huge collection
of death memorabilia.
- How intriguingly creepy.
- Ah, poor Markham's bored.
What about you, Walter?
Last year, you said
you'd do anything for a thrill.
What do you have in mind?
Get down!
Thrilling enough for you, Walter?
- You guys okay?
- I'm fine. Thanks.
We're fine. Shankar might be mad
at Mashburn and Yuri.
- Did you find him?
- Nope. No sign at Shankar's cabin.
The place is like
Buckingham Palace, by the way.
And we searched
all over those woods.
Even the dogs
couldn't pick up a trail.
Have you guys ever been
to an auction?
What? I'm gonna call immigration
see if Shankar's left the country.
Yeah, and see where he parks his boat
or his plane or whatever.
But, boss, he's got no record
and we didn't see anything in that cabin
that would tie him to this...
no gun, ammo, nothing.
Maybe he was never there at all.
And why would he wanna kill
both Yuri and Mashburn?
He doesn't. Actually,
no one wanted to kill Yuri.
What are you talking about?
What if Walter were
the intended target all along?
I mean, he was supposed to die
in that explosion but he didn't.
So the killer follows him
to Chaparral Glen to finish the job.
But the death threat...
it was against Yuri.
Ah, yes, very clever.
Completely threw all of us...
well, almost all of us.
Sorry, Walter.
I have a favor.
Could I borrow that, uh, fancy
little credit card of yours?
Uh, yeah, yeah. What for?
I thought I'd find Shankar.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Did Markham Shankar have
a reason to be angry with you?
Walter.
The takeover
of Yuri's company...
Markham may have been under
the mistaken impression
that he'd receive shares
in return for his help.
But if it was him, wouldn't he
have hired better assassins?
Okay, is there anybody else
who might wanna kill you?
I have lots of enemies, Teresa.
You'd be surprised to hear this
but some people find me annoying.
Yes... My pupils are dilated.
That's not what I was wondering.
Fair enough.
Look, I'll give you a list
of all my nonfriends
but none of them has the stones
to kill me, I promise you.
We'll look into your phone records
and see if anything else comes up.
- Teresa.
- What?
No. You have a...
It's a bullet hole.
It was close. Really close.
Usually, I can buy my way
out of trouble.
Ask my ex-wives.
Don't worry.
We'll keep you safe.
It's procedure to assign
an Agent to protect you.
Oh. Excellent.
- Agent Cho will be here shortly.
- Chicken.
Hello and welcome to Ogilvy.
The auction begins with lot one
a full suit of 16th-century jousting armor.
Let's start the bidding at $30,000.
Do I hear $30,000?
And $30,000's bid off to my left.
Yes, and $31,000.
$31,000. Go $32,000. Thank you.
$32,000 on the right there.
$32,000. Go $33,000. The new bid
at $33,000, at $34,000.
Bid's all the way to $34,000 with the lady
in the front there
$34,000. Go $35,000 if you wish.
$35,000 is bid. $36,000.
New bid at $36,000.
Do I hear $37,000?
Oh, hey, boss.
Markham Shankar has a yacht.
Coast Guard says he sails
tonight, leaving the country.
Camp out on the dock.
Do not leave
until you've questioned Shankar.
Yeah, you got it.
A possible suspect
Mashburn forgot to mention...
his ex-girlfriend, Elsa Struven.
When did they break up?
Two months ago. And apparently,
she wasn't very happy about it.
According to reports, she
threatened him with violence.
Reports?
He filed a complaint?
Uh, no. Published reports,
in the media.
Okay, the tabloids.
She's a German supermodel.
Of course she is.
- Talk to her.
- Okay.
Supermodel.
If I have to do an L.B.O.,
I will, Denise.
But all that debt?
It could crush you.
I'll tell you what.
I'm willing to pay an extra eighth a share
if we ink it by month's end.
Just think about it.
Okay.
Love to Larry and the kids.
You do a lot of business
on the phone?
I do a lot of business.
Phone, texts, e-mails...
doesn't really matter.
Threats work better
on the phone.
That wasn't a threat, Agent Cho.
That was a negotiation.
Hey, I know. We could go to the track
race bikes for a couple of hours.
- Motorcycles?
- Yes.
No. Too exposed.
Okay, then we'll take the Lambo
out for a spin.
It's not safe.
- It has air bags.
- Is it bulletproof?
Can I at least
shoot your gun then?
Patrick. Thank God.
What are the chances of you putting
a party together in, uh... five hours?
Mm... could do, sure.
Sounds fun.
"Invite all of your friends."
I mean, really get
the word out there
'cause you're celebrating, Walter.
You're celebrating.
I am? Great.
Celebrating what?
Oh, uh, I gotta go. Gotta go.
- Uh, uh, $90,000?
- That's $90,000 for lot 10.
And I see $100,000
from the woman in red.
$110,000? Do I hear $110,000?
$110,000 and $120,000?
- $120,000. Thank you. $120,000.
- Uh, $150,000.
Never was any good at math.
I've got $150,000 from
the gentleman in the vest.
How about $160,000? $160,000.
$160,000 is bid.
How about $170,000?
I've got $170,000 and $180,000.
And the gentleman in the front
row, $180,000 is your bid, sir.
You've got the bid at $180,000.
$190,000?
Can we move this thing along?
$200,000.
And $200,000 from our
enthusiastic friend in the back.
Do I hear $210,000?
- Nice day for it, huh?
- Ah, yes.
And whose interests
do you represent?
Well, that's supposed to be
confidential, isn't it?
But what the heck?
Walter Mashburn.
$230,000 if you wish, sir.
$230,000?
$230,000. $230,000.
Do we have $240,000?
- Uh, sir...
- $240,000.
Do we have $240,000?
We have $240,000 right here.
And we also have $250,000.
I know that because I am bidding it.
Do we have $260,000?
- Do we have $260,000, anyone?
- Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait.
Come on, man, you can do
$260,000. I know you can.
Uh, sir?
Let's go.
What about you, sir?
We have $250,000.
No. I want the thing for
$260,000. Can I have it?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Hey, boss.
- Hi.
- I got something.
Uh, so I go to
the ex-girlfriend's penthouse.
She's not there,
but the roommate lets me in
and I find this
on the bedroom wall.
Elsa. Yikes.
Yep. She's for real.
Mashburn called the police
to his house twice
to break up fights between them.
I asked him point-blank
if there was anybody else
who might wanna hurt him.
Why didn't he mention her?
Thank you.
- Sir?
- Oh, please. Thank you.
You're welcome!
What's going on?
It's called a party.
Perhaps you've heard of them.
- You should get yourself a drink.
- I need to talk to Mashburn.
It's here. It looks great,
don't you think?
You still need to speak
to Markham Shankar?
Yeah, Rigsby says he's nowhere
to be found on his yacht. Why?
No reason.
- Teresa, my heroine.
- I need to talk to you.
This woman saved my life,
nearly took a bullet for me.
What the hell is that?
Oh, that's, uh, fragments
of the Porsche Spyder
James Dean died in.
Congratulations, Walter.
You're the owner.
Walter, you son of a bitch.
You outbid me and now you're flaunting it?
You bastard.
- Please step back.
- Meet Markham Shankar.
Uh, I apologize. My bad.
I really needed to talk to you
and you're a very hard man
to track down.
- You lured me here?
- Yeah. Pretty good.
Who the devil
do you think you are?
- The police.
- Cho, you talk to Shankar.
- I've got Mashburn.
- Shankar, did you pull that stunt...
Ladies and gentlemen,
quick announcement...
I'd like you to give
a very warm welcome
to Walter's new girlfriend
number one...Teresa Lisbon!
Hi, Teresa.
- Hi.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Oh, I'm gonna kill him.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- You, too. Hi.
- Sir, we just have a few questions.
- Yes, we certainly do.
Marie Bajoran...
what's her favorite color?
- Now how would I know that?
- Mr. Shankar, do you own a rifle?
I heard about
the attack on Walter.
It was a terrible thing. So hard
to find a good club these days.
And, yes, I do own several rifles.
What of it?
If I were to kill him I'd do the civilized
thing and hire a professional.
What kind of music
does she like?
I have no idea.
Did you believe Mr. Mashburn
cheated you
in the takeover
of Yuri Bajoran's company?
Yes, but helping to destroy Yuri
was its own reward.
Anything else?
Did she prefer Chinese
or Italian for dinner?
Me, personally... Kung Pao chicken.
Although, I do like a sweet corn ravioli
with a white wine sauce. Very nice.
Is this man on medication, perhaps?
No, I'm not. You weren't
having an affair with her?
Ah. Yes, I see.
Now why would you not
simply ask that to begin with?
Fun.
The answer is no. I do enjoy
seducing other men's wives
but Marie and Yuri
were madly in love.
Not exactly a target with
much potential, now is it?
No.
Yes. Thank you.
Uh, Cho, all this talk of food...
I'll be at the oyster bar.
Mr. Shankar, where were you yesterday
between 3:00 and 5:00 p.m.?
- Drink?
- No.
So my friends say
because you saved my life
that means you own me.
They have a return policy?
Oh, come on. Why so cranky
on such a beautiful night?
Well, Walter,
remember when I asked you
if there was anyone
who wanted you dead
anyone else who might have
been mad at you?
- Elsa Struven, maybe?
- Elsa? Oh, yeah, she was mad.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, it's not exactly
breaking news.
My girlfriends are all mad
by the time we break up.
I can't imagine why.
Hey. You have to be nice to me.
No, I don't.
I'm a citizen.
You're a public servant.
I'm off duty now.
I upset you, don't I?
Upset me? No.
Irritate me a little? Maybe.
Why?
You're egotistical.
You're arrogant.
You're entitled and rich.
When do we get
to the bad stuff?
- Walter, no!
- Elsa, what are you, nuts?
- I guess this means we're even.
- Yeah.
Uh, enough.
Elsa, calm down.
Some people never change.
Modeling pays well, Elsa.
You could have easily hired
someone to blow up Mashburn.
And assassinate him
at Chaparral Glen.
But your guy failed
so you took it up yourself
to kill him with this.
What, Walter?
I would never hurt Walter.
I love Walter, and he love me.
It was you I was going to kill,
you little slut.
- Excuse me?
- You kissed him.
I did not.
I didn't.
- You were about to.
- I did not kiss him.
None of my business.
You are totally wrong for him.
So little and bony.
Well, she does have
a damaged intensity
that some people
might find attractive.
Elsa, you've admitted to assault
with a deadly weapon on a cop.
You could get ten years
if you don't cooperate.
Now who did you hire and are
they still after Walter?
Cooperate? So you can tell
Walter what a hero you are
how you save him from me.
And then he kiss you again, huh?
That is what you want, bitch?
No. Go suck your own face.
I don't cooperate.
What are you doing?
Getting familiar.
You were at Walter's to watch
over him, weren't you?
To keep him safe
from women like Lisbon.
- Yes.
- That's okay.
You're very well-groomed
for a crazy person.
Not a hair out of place.
Careful, meticulous.
You document his protection,
don't you?
You show him
how much you love him
and how wrong he is
to not love you back.
You probably keep an album
somewhere. No, not an album.
Where's her cell phone?
So Elsa has over 300 photos
of Mashburn on her phone.
Mashburn on his yacht
Mashburn at a charity event
Mashburn having lunch
with some guy
Mashburn having drinks
with another guy. Hang on.
Go back.
- That's Garth Drucker.
- Yuri Bajoran's Head of Security?
What the hell is Drucker doing having drinks
with his boss' archenemy?
Jane, do you mind?
Uh, Rigsby told me about
Walter and Drucker.
Mashburn's been deceiving us
from the get-go.
Mm, yeah, it should have been obvious
that they knew each other.
Garth Drucker's bank records.
For the past six months he's been
receiving payments of $50,000
from one of Mashburn's
holding companies, a payoff.
Walter's a bad boy.
So what?
Corporate espionage
happens all the time.
He said he'd never been
to Yuri's company before.
He was there a few days ago.
Drucker let him in.
This is from security footage.
I found it at Drucker's house.
He must have been keeping it
as insurance.
Bottom line is, Mashburn
could've planted that bomb.
That's a cool photo.
- Is this funny to you?
- No, not at all.
How do you explain the sniper, then?
Is that a mislead?
Exactly. Mashburn makes us
think he's the target.
He's smart.
Maybe he's that smart.
- Tell me I'm wrong.
- You're wrong.
- Why?
- The sniper very nearly killed you.
Walter wouldn't let that happen
at least I believed that
he wouldn't let that happen.
And on the other hand,
we have the problem of motive.
Walter made a really good case
for wanting to keep Yuri alive
to humiliate him,
so what's his motive to kill?
Not what...
Who.
- Is Walter still in love with you?
- What?
Well, you wouldn't talk
about it before.
It's about guilt, isn't it?
You broke his heart.
Why does any of this
matter now?
Please, it's important.
Do you think Walter may have
been jealous of you and Yuri?
Walter was different
back then.
Sweet.
The night I gave back his ring
and told him about Yuri
I could see something crack
inside him.
He spent
the next half dozen years
dating and often marrying
the most dreadful bimbos.
He does have questionable taste
in women.
Some men are like that
with that first great love.
Their... heart breaks
and the pieces never fit back
together quite the same way.
I'm... I'm very sorry I hurt Walter.
We think that
there's a possibility
that Walter may have been
involved in the bombing.
No. No, I-I don't believe that.
Well, it's quite simple, really.
I mean, you stage an attack.
You appear to be the victim.
No one suspects the victim.
You have something to add?
That night, Walter said
he'd win me back
no matter how long it took.
Mrs. Bajoran, I have a plan,
but I'm gonna need your help.
Of course.
You're gonna confront Walter
and when he looks into your eyes
if he did this for you,
he won't be able to hide it.
- I wanna talk to him first.
- Well...
Okay. Uh, she's... she's gonna
talk to him first.
Of course you can have
the car, Markham.
What am I gonna do
with James Dean's car?
Yeah, I'll send the paperwork
over today.
You make the check out
to my favorite charity, okay?
Yeah. I gotta go.
Teresa, a pleasure.
Hey, I would have been happy
to come to your office.
- Coulda watched you work.
- That would have been awkward.
Listen, if this is
about last night...
it would have been awkward
because I was investigating you.
I know about you and Drucker.
Oh, look, that was industrial
espionage, pure and simple.
Did you kill Yuri?
Hang on. We're back to that?
You think I did it?
If you did, I gotta hand it
to you, it was smart.
You sure fooled me.
You're wrong.
Look, Teresa, I know
you have trust issues...
You don't know
anything about me.
Sure, I do. You were raised in
Chicago. Your mom was a nurse.
Your dad was a fireman. You have
three brothers... Thomas, James...
you checked me out.
Listen to me.
I am this close... this close
to arresting you for murder.
You know what?
I'm gonna go inside.
I'm gonna make myself
a stiff drink
and I really hope you'll join me
so that we can talk about this.
If you did this thing, we'll find the proof.
You know we will.
And it's just a matter of time
before I put you away.
I expect nothing less, Teresa.
Hey, Lisbon.
Where's Walter going?
- In the house.
- Perfect. I'll go get him.
I can't believe
Walter did this.
I'm sorry.
It's a lot to handle.
It's all right.
You're upset.
So are you, Miss Lisbon.
Why is that?
Lisbon! Help!
Jane, you all right?
He hit me.
Did Mashburn
say anything to you?
Just that he'd never risk
going to jail
he has a lot of money
in overseas accounts
and he'd be happy
to live there.
Oh, except we know that
he hasn't left the country.
We've frozen his bank accounts
and every cop in the state's
looking for him.
Mrs. Bajoran, thank you for coming.
Why don't you have a seat?
No sign of Walter yet?
Just his car. We found it abandoned
a few miles from his palatial mansion.
We'll find him. I promise.
And you can help.
You know Mashburn
better than anybody.
We found this
on the seat of his car.
Do you know what it means?
"G-F-M-C-A-1710."
I don't know.
An address of some kind.
- Address to where?
- I don't know.
I'm... I'm sorry, Agent Lisbon.
It's been too long.
I-I don't know Walter anymore.
That's obvious to me now.
Walter! Turn around.
I win!
Not so much, Yuri.
No.
Drop it, Bajoran! Now.
Jane, you can come out now.
Yuri Bajoran!
You're looking delightfully
not-so-blown-up by a bomb.
Very clever of you, I must say.
No one suspects a dead man.
Well, almost no one.
You staged all this... Mashburn running...
just to lure me out.
Well, not bad
for a state employee, huh?
Uh, consultant, really.
Walter finally beat you.
He was gonna take over your company
and your ego couldn't handle that.
So you put that military experience to use.
Kill Mashburn and Drucker, who betrayed you
then leave the country with Marie.
But Mashburn ruined it
for you, didn't he?
You didn't know that he used
your fake death threat
as a reason to call in Lisbon and myself
and you were stuck.
It was my last chance
before signing that damn contract.
I had to do it then.
Let's do the damn deal, Walter.
"Oh, yeah,
and everything was in place..."
"the bomb, and, what, a little
D.N.A. sprinkled everywhere..."
"To prove that you died
in that explosion?"
Hey, Teresa,
while you're here...
"You set the timer
and got out of there."
"You timed it
almost perfectly."
But Walter escaped.
And then you missed him
again in Chaparral Glen.
Mashburn's a cockroach.
He wouldn't die.
Now I have a question for you, Mr. Jane.
How did you know?
"Yuri's toupees?"
Yes, in his bedroom
he had five heads
and only two toupees.
Fine, he was wearing one.
That leaves still two missing
and only one person would
have, uh, such a need for...
Such a personal object.
Yuri took them?
Yeah. Yeah, I guess,
uh, you find a good rug
you, uh, get
very connected to it.
Thank you for your help
in, uh, catching him.
- Oh. Not at all. It was fun.
- Mm. Yeah. Hmm.
Sorry. It was your idea.
Though I still can't believe
that Marie wanted me dead.
You have a knack
for picking 'em.
Almost forgot.
Your credit card.
Thank you.
Patrick, hang on.
One question.
Do you think
Teresa believed it...
that I was the killer?
Yeah, she did for a minute there
but I wouldn't think anything of it.
- We caught lady MacBeth?
- Yeah, at the Canadian border.
Was just gonna come tell the boss.
- Where is she?
- Don't know.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
I'm very glad
you came over last night.
Me, too.
I'll call room service,
order some breakfast.
Nah, nah, I can't.
I'm late.
What can I say?
The bastards keep killing people.
Well, when am I
gonna see you again?
Aren't you going
to Europe tomorrow?
Oh. Two months.
Got board meetings.
Well, there you go then.
It was nice seeing you, Walter.
Can't believe I'm a one-night stand
for Dirty Harry.
Yeah, well, I'd leave you cab fare
but you probably got that covered, right?
Bye, Teresa.
Good-bye, Walter.
Lisbon. Yeah.
Okay, liaise with Costa Mesa P.D.
Put a lid on the crime scene.
You and Cho start canvassing.
It's a crowded neighborhood.
Somebody saw something.